advisorkhoj.com 2015-03-18

# Privacy policy|First Online Directory for Financial Advisors|Advisorkhoj

Dial An Advisor 

#### 076761-76761

Are you a   
**Financial Advisor?**

Search by:

Service, City & Location 

Name 

Locate by Pincode

****

Privacy of information of users is important to us. This privacy statement outlines how we collect information from you, when you register as a user at _www.advisorkhoj.com_ ("website" / "site") and what we do with that information. 

When you browse through the pages of the website, read or download information, we may collect, note or analyze details about your visit such as: 

  * Address of your server

  * Your operating system, domain name and the type of web browser you use

  * The date and time of your visit to the website

  * Whether you have visited the website previously

  * What pages of the website you accessed and what you downloaded

  * Your usage pattern and characteristics.

This information we collect relates also to your server or PC and not necessarily about you yourself. 

The information we collect will be used within _www.advisorkhoj.com_ to help us improve our online services keeping in mind your needs, and to help us to provide you faster navigation and access to the various sections of the website. We may disclose this information to other persons for these purposes or for related purposes, including to information-technology companies who assist / may assist us in constructing, designing and maintaining the website. 

We may also collect your personal details including your credit card details (in case of payment through Auto debit mode) while registering you as a user or subscriber of our various online services or if you email us with a comment or query. 

###  Your details will be used: 

  * To display your details that will be read by other users

  * To answer your comment or query

  * To monitor our responses to you

  * For our internal sales and marketing analysis

  * To facilitate payment through Auto debit mode

We may also contact you to follow up on your order or request, if any, or to provide you with further information about our products and services which may be of interest to you. Where we need to send you any documents, we may disclose your personal details to the mailing houses, printers or document management providers which _www.advisorkhoj.com_ uses so that they can forward the documents to you on our behalf. 

We may share information we collect via the website to other members of any of our other project/ group company who may use the same to provide you with information on various products and services which may be of interest to you. 

If you want to find out what personal information (if any) we hold in respect of you which has been collected through the website, or if you wish to update or correct your personal information, please contact us. 

### Collection of information

The user represents that he is fully aware that in the course of using this website or in the process of subscribing to the products and services or part of it, _www.advisorkhoj.com_ may obtain information relating to the user, including information about his/her credit card and personal information for facilitating payment on auto debit basis which is of a confidential nature. Advisorkhoj.com does not collect personal information about the user except when such users specifically provide such information on a voluntary basis. For example, such information may be collected through the registration process for subscribing to services or in connection with contest submission, message boards, suggestions & voting/polling activities. This information may be stored by www.advisorkhoj.com or its affiliate(s) and used by _www.advisorkhoj.com_ and will be kept confidential. Personal information on users will not be used or otherwise transferred to unaffiliated third parties without the approval of the user. 

### Privacy commitments

_www.advisorkhoj.com_ is strongly committed to protecting the privacy of its users and has taken all necessary and reasonable measures to protect the confidentiality of the users information and its transmission through the world wide web and it shall not be held liable for disclosure of the confidential information when in accordance with this Privacy Commitment or in terms of the agreements, if any, with the users. Employees of _www.advisorkhoj.com_ will not discuss the business affairs of any user with any other employee, except on a strict need-to-know basis. 

### Use of Information

Advisorkhoj.com undertakes not to disclose the information provided by the users to any person, unless such action is necessary to: 

  * Conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process such as requests of the government, court, tribunal, authority or other regulatory agency and/or required by any law;

  * Protect and defend rights, interests or property of _www.advisorkhoj.com_ or its affiliate(s);

  * Enforce the terms and conditions under which its products and/or services are sold; or

  * Act to protect the interests of www.advisorkhoj.com, its affiliate(s), or its members, constituents or of other persons.

_www.advisorkhoj.com_ may use and/ or share the information provided by the users as it may deem necessary with its affiliate(s) and third parties for providing services and any service-related activities in order to serve you better. In this regard it may be necessary to disclose the user information to one or more agents and contractors of _www.advisorkhoj.com_, and their sub-agents or sub-contractors, but such agents, sub-agents, contractors and sub-contractors will be required to use such information only for the stipulated services. 

_www.advisorkhoj.com_ may disclose the user's personal information to government, court, tribunals, authorities or other regulatory agency and/ or as may be required by the law to comply with their bonafide request. In either case Advisorkhoj.com shall be bound by and shall at all times have the legal right to disclose any or all personal information given by the user to it and Advisorkhoj.com shall not be held responsible or liable for any eventuality, loss or damage to the user that may arise out of such action on its part. 

Further, some of the user information is maintained in marketing database of Advisorkhoj.com. _www.advisorkhoj.com_ may contact a user either by post, or by telephone or e-mail primarily as a follow-up to the request/enquiry of the user or to answer any questions. _www.advisorkhoj.com_ may also contact a user from time to time in respect of other products and services that may be of interest to users. If a user does not wish to receive information about these products or services, the user may simply contact _www.advisorkhoj.com_.by phone, e-mail or post and communicate its desire not to receive information on these products or services. 

_www.advisorkhoj.com_ may inform advertisers of information on user's behavior and characteristics showing interest in various areas of the _www.advisorkhoj.com_ website as well as number of users that have been exposed to or clicked on their advertising banner. _www.advisorkhoj.com_ will provide only aggregate data from such analysis done by it to third parties. Also, users should be aware that _www.advisorkhoj.com_ may sometimes permit third parties to offer subscription and/or registration-based services through _www.advisorkhoj.com_ . _www.advisorkhoj.com_ is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties and users should check the applicable privacy policy of such party when providing personally identifiable information. 

### Opt-Out 

If, at any time after registering for information or subscribing to any of our services, you wish to discontinue receiving information from us or you wish to opt out of our marketing or promotional emails, phone calls or discontinue receiving any other direct communication from us, please either click on the "unsubscribe" link available in the service/promotional/marketing emails or send us your request to unsubscribe at [_connect@advisorkhoj.in_](mailto:connect@advisorkhoj.in)

Policy against advertising  _www.advisorkhoj.com_ website using unsolicited email messages

_www.advisorkhoj.com_ ensures that all emails promoting _www.advisorkhoj.com_ or its services or the domains owned by it are sent only to subscribers who have agreed to receive such messages. _www.advisorkhoj.com_ prohibits any advertising of its brand and Website using unsolicited email messages. Any non compliance with this policy would cause partnership termination and/or affiliate account termination. 

If you feel that you have received unsolicited emails from _www.advisorkhoj.com_ and would like to register a complaint, please contact us at [_connect@advisorkhoj.in_](mailto:connect@advisorkhoj.in). We will on a best effort basis investigate all complaints related to unsolicited email messages. 

### Security

The user shall cooperate with _www.advisorkhoj.com_ in order to ensure the security of the information, and we recommend that the users necessarily choose their passwords carefully such that no unauthorized access is made by a third party. The users should undertake not to disclose their password to anyone or keep any written or other record of the password such that a third party could access it. 

### Payment through credit card

In case of annual / other subscription to services through online card payments including on auto debit, _www.advisorkhoj.com_ may obtain private information from the Subscriber including but not limited to date of birth, card number, card expiry date and such other details as may be required by the online payment gateway or as required under any law for the time being in force. 

In such cases, _www.advisorkhoj.com_ shall take all measures including following such security practices and procedures designed to protect all private information obtained from the Subscriber from unauthorized access, damage, use, modification, disclosure or impairment, as may be deemed necessary and reasonable or as may specified by any law for the time being in force. 

### Cookies :

Users are also aware that non-personal information and data may be automatically collected through the standard operation of internet servers or through the use of "cookies" by _www.advisorkhoj.com_."Cookies" are small text files a web site can use to recognize repeat users, facilitate the user's ongoing access to and use of the site and allow a site to track usage behavior and compile aggregate data that will allow content improvements and targeted advertising 

Cookies are not programs that come onto a user's system and damage files. Generally, cookies work by assigning a unique number to the user that has no meaning outside the assigning site. Users are also hereby being made aware that _www.advisorkhoj.com_ cannot control the use of cookies or the resulting information by advertisers or third parties hosting data for _www.advisorkhoj.com_. If a user does not want information collected through the use of cookies, there is a simple procedure in most browsers that allows the user to deny or accept the cookie feature; however, users should note that cookies may be necessary to provide the user with certain features (e.g., customized delivery of information) available from _www.advisorkhoj.com_. 

the right to change this policy at any time by notifying users of the existence of a new privacy statement. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

### Third Party Advertising 

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. 

Please note that this Privacy Statement does not extend to third party sites linked to this website. 

### Amendments 

_www.advisorkhoj.com_ reserves the right to modify the whole or some sections of this Privacy Statement at any time. Please check this statement from time to time for any changes. 

### References 

  * to 'you, 'your' and 'yours' are references to the person(s) accessing this website.

  * to 'we', 'us' and 'our' are references to mean individually and collectively _www.advisorkhoj.com_, Gamechanger Business Servcies (I) Pvt. Ltd., and its directors, officers and employees.

### Contact 

You may contact us at: 

GAMECHANGER BUSINESS SERVICES (I) PVT. LTD. 

304/B-62, 10th Main, 5th Block, Jayanagar 

Bangalore - 560041 (India) 

Telephone : 91-80-41706980 

Fax : 91-80-41706980 

Email : [_connect@advisorkhoj.in_](mailto:connect@advisorkhoj.in)
